Don't look inside me without
permission. I hate it...
Brat.
Then come down from there,
and I'll look down on you!
Jujutsu Kaisen
Episode 6:  After Rain
You're being awfully hostile, aren't you?
Damn straight I am.
You just killed me.
This is the thanks I get for fixing your arm?
Yeah, and you ripped out
my heart right after that!
Is this Hell?
I'm not sure I can accept being
stuck with you even after death.
This works out, though.
I'll make you cry!
Hope you're ready for this!
He was aiming for where I stood?
You fell for it!
I got you!
Huh?
Man, you're boring.
I thought I landed that one perfectly!
Damn it!
This isn't the afterlife.
It's my Innate Domain.
Innate Domain?
That thing Fushiguro was talking about?
You could also say we're in my mind.
In other words, we're not dead yet.
If you'll accept my conditions,
I'll fix your heart and bring us back to life.
Cocky bastard.
You act all big, but I know
you don't want to die, either.
The situation's changed.
In the near future,
I'll be able to see something interesting.
I have two conditions.
One: when I chant "Extension," you'll
hand over your body for one minute.
Two: you'll forget this promise.
No way.
I don't know what your goal is,
but it's shady as hell.
After what you did this time, I finally get it.
You're evil.
I'm not lending you my body again.
Then I'll promise that I won't kill or
injure anyone during that minute.
So annoying.
Like I can believe you!
It's not about whether you believe me or not.
This is a pact.
A geas.
I'll be the one punished if I break it.
If you pursue selfish gain beyond
your means, you'll earn retribution.
I'm pretty sure you've
experienced that for yourself.
It wasn't a problem before!
Huh? Oh...
That time I wanted to switch, too.
And you were just doing
as that sorcerer told you to.
A pact founded in mutual interest.
That's one of the key factors
behind all jujutsu.
Fine, then. So move.
I'll accept your conditions.
I don't know what you're trying to do,
but it means I'll come back to life!
Like hell I'd say that. Bring me back
to life without any conditions.
It's your fault I died in the first place.
Then how about this?
We'll fight to the death, and if you win,
I'll do it without conditions.
If I win, you come back
to life under my conditions.
Sure! I'll beat you to—
You know,
I have a bad personality.
I know.
Ijichi, expect a hard forehead flick later.
F-Forehead flick?
Being a teacher isn't my style.
Do you know why I decided
to teach at this school?
Ask me.
Why did you?
Because I have a dream.
A dream?
Yup.
As you can see in this case with Yuuji,
the top of the jujutsu world is a den of vice.
Conservative fools. Traditional
fools. Arrogant fools.
Just plain fools.
It's a bargain sale on rotten mikan.
I want to reset that garbage jujutsu world.
Murdering everyone at the
top would be an easy task.
But they would just get replaced.
It wouldn't bring a revolution.
And if I did that, no one would follow me.
That's why I chose education.
To raise up strong, clever comrades.
That's also why I occasionally
tossed my missions to my students.
It's tough love.
Are you sure you don't
just want to slack off?
They're all talented.
Especially the third-year, Hakari,
and the second-year, Okkotsu.
They'll become jujutsu
sorcerers on a par with me.
Yuuji was one of those, as well.
Hey, you two.
I'm about to get started.
Are you just gonna watch from there?
Whoa, I'm completely naked!
G-G-G-Gojou-san!
H-H-H-H-H-H-He's alive!
Ijichi, be quiet.
I'm kind of disappointed.
Um, I'm embarrassed to ask, but who are you?
Yuuji!
In the meantime,
put this on!
Welcome back.
Yeah. Good to be back!
Ugh, I'll have to revise the reports.
No, leave them as-is.
I want to give Yuuji time to gain the minimum
power necessary before he's targeted again.
Sorry, Shouko, but could you leave
Yuuji listed as dead on the records?
So you plan to keep Itadori
completely hidden away?
No, I'll have him make his comeback
in time for the Exchange Event.
Why?
The reason is simple.
No one's allowed to take the events
of youth away from young people.
I bet everyone will be surprised.
Not anyone.
Starting right now, I'm ditching work.
I've always had a strong
sense of responsibility.
Onii-chan.
I've been saving up my earnings so I can
send my four younger sisters to college, too.
Aniki.
Niini.
Onii-sama.
But even I can't fight my survival instinct.
If I go near that table, I'll die!
Gojou Satoru.
I wonder if we could kill him
if we joined forces.
Either he'd flutter out of your grasp,
or worst case, you'd all get exorcised.
I would recommend you pour energy
into sealing him rather than killing him.
Seal him?
Do you have a lead?
We'll use the special-grade
cursed object, Prison Realm.
Prison Realm?
Table 5 hasn't ordered anything at all.
Someone go hurry him up.
He's taking up a whole table by himself.
Sorry, boss, but I quit!
Huh? What?!
Hey! Hold on a minute!
You have that detestable thing?!
Our AC is running, isn't it?
Jougo, don't get too excited.
You'll make it hot in here.
Sir, have you decided on your order?
I wish you wouldn't cause
too much commotion.
This is hardly anything.
What the...
I'm glad we didn't choose
an expensive restaurant.
Getou, how strong am I
in terms of Sukuna's fingers?
At a low estimate,
I'd say eight or nine fingers?
That's plenty. Give me the Prison Realm!
I'll add it to my collection.
In return, I will...
kill Gojou Satoru.
Help—
Jujutsu Kaisen
By the time we arrived on the scene,
your son was already dead.
To be honest, I was skeptical about
saving any of the people in there.
But my friend was different.
He wasn't successful,
but he tried to bring your son's body back
for you after we confirmed his death.
Please.
Okazaki Tadashi
Take this, at least.
I'm sorry we weren't
able to save Tadashi-san.
It's all right. Don't apologize.
I'm the only one who will
mourn his passing, anyway...
You're late, Megumi.
Kelp.
What were you doing?
What does it matter?
Zenin-senpai...
What kinds of people do you want
to save as a jujutsu sorcerer?
Huh?
It's not like I care if my actions save anyone.
I shouldn't have asked.
What?!
Fushiguro!
Quit asking interview prep questions!
Switch with me!
I'm sick of these school uniforms!
Let me go buy some cute tracksuits!
Here we go!
What are those two doing?
Falling practice.
Mustard leaf.
You're both weak in
close quarters, after all.
So first...
Land a blow on us.
We'll talk after that.
You're a head above the rest when
it comes to close combat, Yuuji.
So what you need to learn right now
is how to control cursed energy,
as well as the bare minimum
of jujutsu knowledge.
Smile
What's the matter?
ee-hee
Oh, I figured you'd be the best person
to train me, so I'm just happy.
I'm weak, and I couldn't save anybody.
Worse, I nearly killed Fushiguro.
As I am now, I won't be able to face them.
I want to become strong.
Teach me to be the strongest.
You've got a keen eye.
Sensei, you're the one who
called yourself the strongest.
All right, first, take a look at
those drink cans over there.
This is with cursed energy,
and this is with a cursed technique.
I see. I don't get it.
Right, well...
Think of cursed energy as electricity,
and cursed techniques as appliances.
Electricity by itself is hard to use, right?
That's why we run electricity through
appliances to achieve various results.
Here, I just fired off pure cursed energy.
Here, I channeled cursed energy
into a cursed technique
to activate it and twist the can with jujutsu.
In other words, I'm about to learn
a very, very good cursed technique?!
No, you can't use cursed techniques.
Huh?!
Setting aside simple shikigami and barriers,
cursed techniques are fundamentally etched
into your body from the day you're born.
So the power of a jujutsu sorcerer
is roughly 80% innate talent.
You okay?
I just thought I'd be able to pull off thunder
or fire or a power bomb or something.
You can pull off a power bomb. Ohnita's, right?
This sucks.
I wanted to pull off a Spirit Gun or
Bankai, or Rasengan, or a Dodon Ray.
You just can't use them yet.
Eventually Sukuna's cursed techniques
will be engraved into your body.
I wanted to fire off a Kamehameha.
Let's just ignore what you can't do!
We're going to enhance your strengths.
This totally sucks.
We'll get you to imbue your
fighting style with cursed energy.
I'm way more scared of someone
who can force their way through with
the basics than I am of inferior jujutsu.
Like I just said, your talent
for close combat is top-notch.
But wait! I can already do that!
Get up.
Back then, I somehow managed
to get the hang of it.
Then give it a try.
Hit me here.
Not that you actually can.
Don't blame me if you get hurt.
Just hurry up and do it.
That didn't have any
cursed energy behind it.
How?!
Negative emotions are
the source of cursed energy.
In the incident you're referring to, you were
probably brimming with anger and fear.
So you have to constantly be
flipping out to use cursed energy?
Now that you mention it,
Fushiguro's always a bit snappy.
Demon Dogs!
Not like that.
What's the matter?
I just got really irritated.
Huh?
No, not at you.
Salmon roe.
There's only a month and a half until
the Exchange Event, so no dawdling.
Here, you can try the long one next.
This actually feels pretty good.
Everyone's trained to produce cursed
energy using the faintest sparks of emotion.
They've also trained on how to not waste
cursed energy when emotions are flaring, too.
There are several methods to train this.
I'll be having you use
a pretty exhausting one.
L-Like what?
Watching movies.
Watching movies?
Yup.
Everything from masterpieces to C-grade
horror films and terrible French movies.
You'll be watching them nonstop
as long as you're awake.
Of course, you won't just be watching them.
You'll be watching them with this guy.
What's with the cute but creepy doll?
It's cute?
It's a cursed corpse the principal made.
Ah, I knew it! It has his sense!
And? I don't understand
what you're getting at here.
Don't be hasty, now. You'll see soon.
That cursed corpse will wake up
and attack you, just like that,
if you don't keep pouring a set
amount of cursed energy into it.
Ow!
Like I just said, we have all
kinds of movies available here.
Heart-throbbers, thrillers, exciting ones,
ones that'll make you cry,
laugh, or feel disgusted.
Yawn
Your first goal is to watch an entire movie,
from start to finish,
without waking the cursed corpse.
Num   Num
This trains you to maintain a steady
output of cursed energy,
no matter what emotions you feel.
You can't use too much or too little.
I have it set to the faint level of cursed
energy you can produce right now,
but it'll steadily start
demanding greater output,
so don't let your guard down.
I couldn't let it down even if I wanted to.
What do you want to start with?
I recommend this one.
The heroine's annoying,
but she dies spectacularly in the end.
Major spoilers.
I say we start off with an action—
Oh, come on!
Hey, even if you're irritated,
keep the cursed energy steady.
Carrying cursed tools, huh?
I agree with supplementing
my close combat with weapons,
but with my cursed technique, I want to
be able to free up both hands at any time.
With swords, you lose time sheathing them.
Zenin-senpai, you often carry more
than two around with you, right?
How do you do that?
I make Panda carry them.
I shouldn't have asked, part two.
Some sorcerers keep cursed spirits
that can store and retrieve objects.
He can't do that. It's a rare thing.
And it takes time to tame them, as well.
But if you find any, let me know.
A year's supply of Calpas.
I don't get it, though.
Why...
did you run back then?
What a waste of talent.
I have the potential to beat special-grades?
Is that what he meant by that?
Tuna, tuna.
Huh? What?
Senpai.
I think I can do it.
Ura-Hara! Where's Ura-Hara?!
Underground?!
Do I cut the red wire or the blue wire?
You know, in the area where I used to live,
the designated trash bags...
Hey, what are you going on about right now?
...were red for plastic trash
and blue for combustible trash.
I always thought, shouldn't it be the opposite?
It should be red! Anyone would go with red!
I'll trust you.
Don't do that while I'm drinking soda!
Don't drink it, then.
But you gotta have chips and soda
when watching movies at home!
That's true.
Okay, I have some business to deal with.
Just keep hanging in there.
Will this really make me stronger?
Oh, right.
Did you talk to Sukuna while you were dead?
Talk?
When he fixed your heart, did he
propose any conditions or contracts?
Oh, I think we did talk about something...
But I can't remember what it was.
I see.
We have a bit of time before your
appointment with the principal.
Did you want to stop anywhere?
It's fine.
I'll show up early for a change.
Stop the car.
Huh? Right here?
Go on ahead.
Huh? A-Are you testing me?
You're not going to hit me if
I actually go on ahead, are you?
Just what do you think I am?
In that case...
Now...
Who are you?
Juju Stroll
Gojou Satoru's Go Go Gojou
It's Gojou Satoru's Go Go Gojou!
Today we're at my alma mater,
Tokyo Metropolitan Jujutsu
Technical High School.
Satoru-sensei
Oh? We already have a boy in trouble.
Yuuji
Is he a new student?
It looks like he can't produce
cursed energy very well.
Let's give him some advice.
Imagine you're walking down a narrow path.
Before you is a row of college boys.
They haven't noticed you at all.
You want to kill them, don't you? So you...
Shut up.
Episode 7:
Assault
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org